Guide to the New York University Archives Biographical Files MC.317
New York University Archives
- Holden, Matthew Jr., undated (Box 81)
- Holladay, Ryan, undated (Box 81)
- Holland, Daniel M., undated (Box 81)
- Hollander, I. Fred (Rabbi), undated (Box 81)
- Hollander, Charles S., undated (Box 81)
- Hollander, Sam, undated (Box 81)
- Hollander, Lawrence J., undated (Box 81)
- Howeb, Arthur, undated (Box 81)
- Holley, Alexander Lyman, undated (Box 81)
- Hollinshead, Merrill, undated (Box 81)
- Hollinshead, Taylor, undated (Box 81)
- Holman, Nat, undated (Box 81)
- Holman, Jr Wayne J., undated (Box 81)
- Holmberg-Spongberg, Viola, undated (Box 81)
- Holmes, David, undated (Box 81)
- Holmes, Robert, undated (Box 81)
- Hoit, Emmett, undated (Box 81)
- Holt, Robert, undated (Box 81)
- Holtz, Elizabeth Scott, undated (Box 81)
- Holtzman, Elizabeth, undated (Box 81)
- Holtzer, Charles, undated (Box 81)
- Holzer, Stuart, undated (Box 81)
- Holzknecht, Karl J., undated (Box 81)
- Holzman, Robert, undated (Box 81)
- Holzman, Samuel, undated (Box 82)
- Hollister, Paul, undated (Box 82)
- Holly, Frank, undated (Box 82)
- Holmberg, David, undated (Box 82)
- Holmes, Anna, undated (Box 82)
- Holmes, Douglas, undated (Box 82)
- Holmes, H. Frederick, undated (Box 82)
- Holmes, Marguerite, undated (Box 82)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell, undated (Box 82)
- Hone, Philip, undated (Box 82)
- Hook, Sidney, undated (Box 82)
- Hook, Sidney, undated (Box 83)
- Hoopingarner, Newman, undated (Box 83)
- Hoost, Allen John, undated (Box 83)
- Hoover, David F., undated (Box 83)
- Hoover, David, undated (Box 83)
- Hopf, Hans, undated (Box 83)
- Hopf, Harry Arthur, undated (Box 83)
- Hopkins, Nicholas S., undated (Box 83)
- Hopkins, Tredwell H., undated (Box 83)
- Hopper, Edward, undated (Box 83)
- Hopper, U.F., undated (Box 83)
- Hoppock, Robert, undated (Box 83)
- Horkan, Patricia, undated (Box 83)
- Horn, Frederick, undated (Box 83)
- Horn, George A., undated (Box 83)
- Horn, Herald, undated (Box 83)
- Horn, Paul, undated (Box 83)
- Horn, Paul U., undated (Box 83)
- Horne, Herman H., undated (Box 83)
- Hornstein, Benjamin S., undated (Box 83)
- Hornstein, George D., undated (Box 83)
- Hornstein, Lillian Herlands, undated (Box 83)
- Horowitz, Alfred H., undated (Box 83)
- Horowitz, Israel, undated (Box 84)
- Horowitz, Milton, undated (Box 84)
- Horowitz, William, undated (Box 84)
- Horton, Mary Burnett, undated (Box 84)
- Horton, Rod W., undated (Box 84)
- Horvath, Patrick J., undated (Box 84)
- Horwitz, Jay, undated (Box 84)
- Horowitz, Martin, undated (Box 84)
- Horowitz, Murray, undated (Box 84)
- Hotchkiss, George Burton, undated (Box 84)
- Hotchkiss, George B., undated (Box 84)
- Hotchkiss, Robert, undated (Box 84)
- Houghton, Albert R., undated (Box 84)
- Houghton, Dale, undated (Box 84)
- Houghton, Rev George Hendric, undated (Box 84)
- Houghton, Henrietta Fleck, undated (Box 84)
- Howard, Bryce Dallas, undated (Box 84)
- Houk, Dale W., undated (Box 84)
- Houet, Thomas, undated (Box 84)
- Howard, Bronson, undated (Box 84)
- Howard, George, undated (Box 84)
- Howard, J. Scott, undated (Box 84)
- Howard, Lawrence I., undated (Box 84)
- Howard, Mel, undated (Box 84)
- Howard, Paige, undated (Box 84)
- Howarth, Andrew, undated (Box 84)
- Howe, Andrew, undated (Box 84)
- Howe, Tina, undated (Box 84)
- Howell, Paul, undated (Box 84)
- Howland, John, undated (Box 84)
- Howley, Frank Leo, undated (Box 85)
- Howley, Peter A., undated (Box 85)
- Hoydysh, Walter G., undated (Box 85)
- Huang, Alice, undated (Box 85)
- Huang, Kenny, undated (Box 85)
- Hubbard, Harry House, undated (Box 85)
- Hubbell, Dr. Alan Horbes, undated (Box 85)
- Huber, Harold, undated (Box 85)
- Hubin, Dorothea, undated (Box 85)
- Hudson, George E., undated (Box 85)
- Huebener, Theodore, undated (Box 85)
- Hug, Elsie A., undated (Box 85)
- Hughes, Robert P., undated (Box 85)
- Hughes, Wandel Lochead, undated (Box 85)
- Hughes, Richard E., undated (Box 85)
- Hull, George H., undated (Box 85)
- Hull, Richard, undated (Box 85)
- Hull, Vernam, undated (Box 85)
- Hulme, Harold, undated (Box 85)
- Humphrey, Hubert, undated (Box 85)
- Hungerford, Arthur, undated (Box 85)
- Hunkins, Maurel, undated (Box 85)
- Hunt, Andrew Dickenson Jr., undated (Box 85)
- Huntingtons, Daniel, undated (Box 85)
- Hupper, Gail, undated (Box 85)
- Huppert, Elmer, undated (Box 85)
- Hurley, Beatrice D., undated (Box 85)
- Hurley, Roy T., undated (Box 85)
- Hurt, Mary Beth S., undated (Box 85)
- Hurvich, Leo M., undated (Box 85)
- Hurwitz, Jerard, undated (Box 85)
- Hurwitz, Leo, undated (Box 85)
- Hussein, King, undated (Box 85)
- Hussey, M.M., undated (Box 85)
- Huston, John C., undated (Box 85)
- Hutner, Simeon, undated (Box 85)
- Hutton, Truman, undated (Box 85)
- Hutton, William T., undated (Box 85)
- Huxtable, Ada Louise, undated (Box 85)
- Hyams, George, undated (Box 85)
- Hyatt, Ann R., undated (Box 85)
- Hyde, Fillmore, undated (Box 85)
- Hyde, W. Lewis, undated (Box 85)
- Hyman, Milton, undated (Box 85)
- Iakovos, Rev., undated (Box 85)
- Iams, Franklin, undated (Box 85)
- Iannizzi, Elizabeth, undated (Box 85)
- Iason, Lawrence, undated (Box 85)
- Ibi, Keiko, undated (Box 85)
- Ice-T, undated (Box 85)
- Ifshien, Fania, undated (Box 85)
- Ignatieff, Michael, undated (Box 85)
- Illefalva, Kalman, undated (Box 86)
- Imhof, Howard E., undated (Box 86)
- Immerman, Isadore, undated (Box 86)
- Inciardi, Salvatore R., undated (Box 86)
- Ingber, Audrey H., undated (Box 86)
- Iglehart, Robert L., undated (Box 86)
- Ikeda, Kentaro, undated (Box 86)
- Imbrie, Andrew, undated (Box 86)
- Ingram, William T., undated (Box 86)
- Ignatow, Archive, undated (Box 86)
- Ionesco, Eugene, undated (Box 86)
- Ipsen, Sylvia Leonard, undated (Box 86)
- Iran, Phun, undated (Box 86)
- Ireland, John B., undated (Box 86)
- Irvin, June N., undated (Box 86)
- Irving, David, undated (Box 86)
- Irwin, Ray Watkins, undated (Box 86)
- Isaacs, Abram Samuel, undated (Box 86)
- Isaacson, Eugene, undated (Box 86)
- Ishikawa, Akira, undated (Box 86)
- Isserman, Richard D., undated (Box 86)
- Isom, Morris P., undated (Box 86)
- Israel, Edouard, undated (Box 86)
- Ivers, Barbara, undated (Box 86)
- Ives, Sumner, undated (Box 86)
- Ivey, John E., undated (Box 86)
- Ivry, Alfred L., undated (Box 86)
- Izman, Nurul Syaheedah Jes, undated (Box 86)
- Jackson, Frederick H., undated (Box 86)
- Jackson, George, undated (Box 86)
- Jackson, Henry, undated (Box 86)
- Jackson, Holils Condict, undated (Box 86)
- Jackson, James and Esther, undated (Box 86)
- Jackson, Judy, undated (Box 86)
- Jackson, Jesse, undated (Box 86)
- Jackson, Theodore C., undated (Box 86)
- Jackson, Thomas Jonathan "Stonewall", undated (Box 86)
- Jackson, Raymond S., undated (Box 86)
- Jacob, H. Myles, undated (Box 86)
- Jacobs, Bernard, undated (Box 86)
- Jacobs, Gerald M., undated (Box 86)
- Jacobs, Harold A., undated (Box 86)
- Jacobs, James, undated (Box 86)
- Jacobs, Lewis, undated (Box 86)
- Jacobs, Roger B., undated (Box 86)
- Jacobs, Stephen A., undated (Box 86)
- Jacobson, Myron, undated (Box 86)
- Jacobziner, Harold, undated (Box 86)
- Jaffa, Herbert C., undated (Box 86)
- Jaffe, D.J., undated (Box 86)
- Jaffe, Leo, undated (Box 86)
- Jaffin, David, undated (Box 86)
- Jahn, George D., undated (Box 87)
- Jahoda, Marie, undated (Box 87)
- James, Debra, undated (Box 87)
- James, Henry, undated (Box 87)
- James, Louis, undated (Box 87)
- James, Philip, undated (Box 87)
- James, Seymour, undated (Box 87)
- James, L. Stanley, undated (Box 87)
- James, Thomas, undated (Box 87)
- James, William, undated (Box 87)
- Jameson, Thomas H., undated (Box 87)
- Janis, J. Harold, undated (Box 87)
- Jansen, Arthur, undated (Box 87)
- Janson, Horst Waldemar, undated (Box 87)
- Jaquith, Stephen M., undated (Box 87)
- Jarke, Matthias, undated (Box 87)
- Jarvik, Robert K., undated (Box 87)
- Jarvinen, Villo O., undated (Box 87)
- Jarvik, Robert Koffler, undated (Box 87)
- Jarvis, N. Leonard, undated (Box 87)
- Jarvis, J. Pitts Jr., undated (Box 87)
- Javits, Jacob K., undated (Box 87)
- Javits, Marian, undated (Box 87)
- Jaspen, Nathan, undated (Box 87)
- Javits, Jacob K., undated (Box 87)
- Jaworski, Edward, undated (Box 87)
- Jay, Stephen, undated (Box 87)
- Jeffers, Cindy, undated (Box 87)
- Jeffries, Leonard, undated (Box 87)
- Jenkins, Carol, undated (Box 87)
- Jenkins, Robert B., undated (Box 87)
- Jenkins, Tamara, undated (Box 87)
- Jenkins, Thomas N., undated (Box 87)
- Jenkins, Andrew, undated (Box 87)
- Jenks, Jeremiah, undated (Box 87)
- Jenrette, Richard, undated (Box 87)
- Jensen, Grady E., undated (Box 87)
- Jeremijenko, Natalie, undated (Box 87)
- Jerry, Keith M., undated (Box 87)
- Jethake, Henry, undated (Box 87)
- Jewett, Constance, undated (Box 87)
- Jiranek, David, undated (Box 87)
- Jobs, Steve, undated (Box 87)
- John, Frederick W., undated (Box 87)
- John, Fritz, undated (Box 87)
- Johnson, Alan, undated (Box 87)
- Johnson, Arnold, undated (Box 87)
- Johnson, Carl, undated (Box 87)
- Johnson, Ebenezer Alfred, undated (Box 87)
- Johnson, E.A.J., undated (Box 87)
- Johnson, James Weldon, undated (Box 87)
- Johnson, Joseph French, undated (Box 88)
- Johnson, Jotham, undated (Box 88)
- Johnson, Lewis O., undated (Box 88)
- Johnson, Lowell, undated (Box 88)
- Johnson, Lyndon Baines, undated (Box 88)
- Johnson, Malcolm, undated (Box 88)
- Johnson, Philip, undated (Box 88)
- Johnson, Robert, undated (Box 88)
- Johnson, Robert T., undated (Box 88)
- Johnson, Robert Underwood, undated (Box 88)
- Johnson, Samuel Frederick, undated (Box 88)
- Johnson, Samuel H., undated (Box 88)
- Johnson, Scott, undated (Box 88)
- Johnson, Stanford L., undated (Box 88)
- Johnson, Stephen, undated (Box 88)
- Johnson, Thomas, undated (Box 88)
- Johnson, John taylor, undated (Box 88)
- Jolie, Angelina, undated (Box 88)
- Jolliffe, Norman, undated (Box 88)
- Jolly, Clifford J., undated (Box 88)
- Jones, Beatrice G., undated (Box 88)
- Jones, Bruce, undated (Box 88)
- Jones, David R., undated (Box 88)
- Jones, Edward P., undated (Box 88)
- Jones, Howard Mumford, undated (Box 88)
- Jones, Julia, undated (Box 88)
- Jones, Karen, undated (Box 88)
- Jones, Mary-ann, undated (Box 88)
- Jones, Merritt, undated (Box 88)
- Jones, Phil, undated (Box 88)
- Jones, Thatcher C., undated (Box 88)
- Jones, Theodore, undated (Box 88)
- Jones, Ward, undated (Box 88)
- Jones, William D., undated (Box 88)
- Jones, Vincent I., undated (Box 88)
- Joo, Won Moon, undated (Box 88)
- Joran, Alvin D., undated (Box 88)
- Jordan, Henry P., undated (Box 88)
- Joseph, Harry, undated (Box 88)
- Joseph, Marc Bamuthi, undated (Box 88)
- Joseph, Rajiv, undated (Box 88)
- Jovanovic, Boyan, undated (Box 88)
- Joyal, Achille A., undated (Box 88)
- Joyce, James Avery, undated (Box 88)
- Judt, Tony, undated (Box 88)
- Juran, Joseph M., undated (Box 88)
- Jurow, Irving H., undated (Box 88)
- Just, Michael H., undated (Box 88)
- Justin, Jules J., undated (Box 88)
- Jutkowitz, Adolph, undated (Box 88)
- Juul, Jesper, undated (Box 88)
- Kabak, Irwin W., undated (Box 88)
- Kabnick, Herbert, undated (Box 88)
- Kadison, Herbert, undated (Box 88)
- Kahn, Alfred Edward, undated (Box 88)
- Kahn, David, undated (Box 88)
- Kahn, Marcel, undated (Box 88)
- Kahn, Martin C., undated (Box 88)
- Kahn, Roger, undated (Box 88)
- Kahn, Dr. Sanders A., undated (Box 88)
- Kagey, Rudolf, undated (Box 88)
- Kaiser, Elmer R., undated (Box 89)
- Kaixi, Wu'er, undated (Box 89)
- Kalb, Milton, undated (Box 89)
- Kalinkowitz, Bernard, undated (Box 89)
- Kalkin, Gary, undated (Box 89)
- Kallenbach, Neville, undated (Box 89)
- Kallmann, Dr. Hartmut, undated (Box 89)
- Kalman, Tibor, undated (Box 89)
- Kalodner, Howard, undated (Box 89)
- Kalos, Malvin H., undated (Box 89)
- Kaminsky, Ralph, undated (Box 89)
- Kamm, Frances Myma, undated (Box 89)
- Kampelman, Max M., undated (Box 89)
- Kanakaratne, N.T.D., undated (Box 89)
- Kane, David S., undated (Box 89)
- Kane, Thomas J. '42A, undated (Box 89)
- Kanfer, Bruce '69, undated (Box 89)
- Kang, Younghill, undated (Box 89)
- Kantrowitz, Adrian, undated (Box 89)
- Kao, J.H.K., undated (Box 89)
- Kapfer, Joane, undated (Box 89)
- Kapfer, W.M.H., undated (Box 89)
- Kaplan, Bernard, undated (Box 89)
- Kaplan, Burton, undated (Box 89)
- Kaplan, Chester, undated (Box 89)
- Kaplan, Donald, undated (Box 89)
- Kaplan, H. Elliot, undated (Box 89)
- Kaplan, Flora Edouwaye S., undated (Box 89)
- Kaplan, Louise, undated (Box 89)
- Kaplan, Neal '61, undated (Box 89)
- Kaplan, Ralph J., undated (Box 89)
- Kaplan, Robert '49, undated (Box 89)
- Kaplan, Seymour, undated (Box 89)
- Kaplan, Stanley and Rita, undated (Box 89)
- Kaplan, Steven, undated (Box 89)
- Kaplan, Werner J., undated (Box 89)
- Kaplow, Jeffrey, undated (Box 89)
- Kapp, Richard, undated (Box 89)
- Kaprow, Allan, undated (Box 89)
- Karasak, Eleanor, undated (Box 89)
- Karchin, Louis, undated (Box 89)
- Karl, Frederick, undated (Box 89)
- Karlen, Delmar, undated (Box 89)
- Karlin, Margaret Fuller '24L, undated (Box 90)
- Karow, Dr. Edward M., undated (Box 90)
- Karowe, Harris E., undated (Box 90)
- Karp, Jonathan, undated (Box 90)
- Karp, Marilyn, undated (Box 90)
- Karp, Samuel, undated (Box 90)
- Karpat, K.H., undated (Box 90)
- Karr, N.A. (Nathaniel), undated (Box 90)
- Kastner, Edward C., undated (Box 90)
- Kastner, Elwood, undated (Box 90)
- Katona, George, undated (Box 90)
- Katsh, Abraham, undated (Box 90)
- Katsh, Abraham Isaac, undated (Box 90)
- Katz, Barbara G., undated (Box 91)
- Katz, Professor Benjamin J., undated (Box 91)
- Katz, Bernard, undated (Box 91)
- Katz, Esther, undated (Box 91)
- Katz, Gary, undated (Box 91)
- Katz, George A. '54, undated (Box 91)
- Katz, Dr. Irwin I., undated (Box 91)
- Katz, Jan Hack, undated (Box 91)
- Katz, Jane, undated (Box 91)
- Katz, Rita Ellix, undated (Box 91)
- Katz, Sanford M., undated (Box 91)
- Katzell, Raymond A., undated (Box 91)
- Kaufman, Charlie, undated (Box 91)
- Kaufman, Dean Edward, undated (Box 91)
- Kaufman, Henry, undated (Box 91)
- Kaufman, Irving, undated (Box 91)
- Kaufman, Lewis C., undated (Box 91)
- Kaufman, Paul D., undated (Box 91)
- Kaufman, Victor, undated (Box 91)
- Kauffmann, Desire, undated (Box 91)
- Kauffman, Stanley, undated (Box 91)
- Kaufmann, Ruth, undated (Box 91)
- Kauffer, H.J., undated (Box 91)
- Kaupelis, Robert, undated (Box 91)
- Kavanagh, Frank Edge, 1901 (Box 192, Folder 25)
- Kavanagh, Thomas C., undated (Box 91)
- Kavesh, Robert A., undated (Box 91)
- Kawamoto, Elso, undated (Box 91)
- Kawamura, Shigekuni, undated (Box 91)
- Kay, Lillian W., undated (Box 91)
- Kay, Dr. Paul, undated (Box 91)
- Kaya, Esin, undated (Box 91)
- Kaye, Judith Smith, undated (Box 91)
- Kaye, Silvia K., undated (Box 91)
- Kazan, Elia, undated (Box 91)
- Kazemi, Farhad, undated (Box 91)
- Kazimiroff, Theodore, undated (Box 91)
- Kazin, Alfred, undated (Box 91)
- Kazmierczak, Antoni, undated (Box 91)
- Kean, Helen Faith, undated (Box 91)
- Keans, Marguerite P., undated (Box 91)
- Kearns, Alexander, undated (Box 91)
- Kearse, Amalya Lyle, undated (Box 91)
- Kearse, Lee Andrew, undated (Box 91)
- Keck, Caroline, undated (Box 91)
- Keck, Sheldon, undated (Box 91)
- Keefe, David, undated (Box 92)
- Keefe, Arthur John, undated (Box 92)
- Keeley, Mary K., undated (Box 92)
- Keenan, D'Elbert, undated (Box 92)
- Keenan, Dr. James J., undated (Box 92)
- Keim, Kevin L., undated (Box 92)
- Keiper, Joseph S., undated (Box 92)
- Keiser, Laurence, undated (Box 92)
- Keiser, Sylvan, undated (Box 92)
- Keightley, David Noel, undated (Box 92)
- Kekes, John, undated (Box 92)
- Kelen, Emery, undated (Box 92)
- Keliher, Alice, undated (Box 92)
- Kellen, Allan, undated (Box 92)
- Kellen, Dr. Herbert, undated (Box 92)
- Keller, Dr. Herbert B., undated (Box 92)
- Kells, Edmund C., undated (Box 92)
- Keller, Joseph B., undated (Box 92)
- Keller, Joseph G., undated (Box 92)
- Kelley, Carmen Webster '31, undated (Box 92)
- Kelley, Dr. Eugene J., undated (Box 92)
- Kelley Family History by Frank Bergen Kelley Class of 1890, undated (Box 92)
- Kelley, John Patrick, undated (Box 92)
- Kelley, Kathleen M., undated (Box 92)
- Kelly, Robin D., undated (Box 92)
- Kelley, Sheila (TSOA '85), undated (Box 92)
- Kelly, C. Christine, undated (Box 92)
- Kelly, Harry M., undated (Box 92)
- Kelly, Howard A. Jr. '63 GPA, '53 E, undated (Box 92)
- Kelly, Orie R., undated (Box 92)
- Kelly, Raymond W., undated (Box 92)
- Kelly, Walter L., undated (Box 92)
- Kelsey, Clarence Hill, undated (Box 92)
- Kempler, Emory, undated (Box 92)
- Kemp, Jack, undated (Box 92)
- Kempin, Emily, undated (Box 92)
- Kempner, Margaret Loeb, undated (Box 92)
- Keneally, Thomas, undated (Box 92)
- Kendler, Howard H., undated (Box 92)
- Kennedy Emma B., undated (Box 92)
- Kennedy, Eugene P., undated (Box 92)
- Kennedy, James D., undated (Box 92)
- Kennedy, Dr. James W., undated (Box 92)
- Kennedy, John F., undated (Box 92)
- Kennedy, John F. Jr., undated (Box 93)
- Kennedy, John Stewart, undated (Box 93)
- Kennedy, Michael, undated (Box 93)
- Kennedy, Moorhead, undated (Box 93)
- Kennedy, Stephen P., undated (Box 93)
- Kenny, Maurice, undated (Box 93)
- Kent, Fred I., undated (Box 93)
- Kentera, Chris W., undated (Box 93)
- Keogh, Eugene, undated (Box 93)
- Keogh, Eugene J. '27C, undated (Box 93)
- Kepecs, Randi, undated (Box 93)
- Kerekes, Gabriel, undated (Box 93)
- Kerkeling, Hape, undated (Box 93)
- Kerley, Robert F., undated (Box 93)
- Kerlinger, Dr. Fred N., undated (Box 93)
- Kerner, Ian, undated (Box 93)
- Kern, Jerome H., undated (Box 93)
- Kerns, J. Alexander, undated (Box 93)
- Kerr, Arnold D., undated (Box 93)
- Kervaire, Dr. Mitchell A., undated (Box 93)
- Kessel, Richard, undated (Box 93)
- Kestenberg, Judith, undated (Box 93)
- Ketefian, Shake, undated (Box 93)
- Keuhl, John, undated (Box 93)
- Keyes, Cheryl, undated (Box 93)
- Keyishian, Janet, undated (Box 93)
- Keys, Samuel R., undated (Box 93)
- Khanga, Yelena, undated (Box 93)
- Kharas, Ralph E., undated (Box 93)
- Kharouba, Ghada, undated (Box 93)
- Kihl, Harold J., undated (Box 93)
- Kilander, Holger Frederick, undated (Box 93)
- Kilduff, Edward, undated (Box 93)
- Kilduff, Ed J. '32A, undated (Box 93)
- Kiley, Robert, undated (Box 93)
- Kilmer, Joyce, undated (Box 93)
- Kim, Daniel Dae, undated (Box 93)
- Kim, Kyung-Won, undated (Box 93)
- Kim, Sam Young, undated (Box 93)
- Kim, Kimball Fiske, undated (Box 93)
- Kim, Le Roy E., undated (Box 93)
- Kim, Morton C., undated (Box 93)
- Kimbrell, Marketa, undated (Box 93)
- Kimara, Mari, undated (Box 93)
- Kimbrough, Spenser, undated (Box 93)
- Kindy, Joan Henry, undated (Box 93)
- King, Bruce, undated (Box 93)
- King, Carol Weiss, undated (Box 93)
- King, Cecil V., undated (Box 93)
- King, Charles W., undated (Box 93)
- King, Coretta Scott, undated (Box 93)
- King, David A., undated (Box 93)
- King, J. David, undated (Box 93)
- King, Lawrence B., undated (Box 93)
- King, Lawrence P., undated (Box 94)
- King, Reverend Dr. Martin Luther, undated (Box 94)
- King, Reno, undated (Box 94)
- King, Willford J., undated (Box 94)
- King, Yolanda, undated (Box 94)
- Kingsley, Norman William, undated (Box 94)
- Kingsley, William Morgan, undated (Box 94)
- Kinnell, Galway, undated (Box 94)
- Kinney, Emily, undated (Box 94)
- Kinsella, John J., undated (Box 94)
- Kintisch, Irving L. '46, undated (Box 94)
- Kinzel, A.B., undated (Box 94)
- Kiorpes, Lynne, undated (Box 94)
- Kirby, Daniel B., undated (Box 94)
- Kirby, James Cordell, undated (Box 94)
- Kirby, Kitty, undated (Box 94)
- Kirby, Michael, undated (Box 94)
- Kirkland, Carolina, undated (Box 94)
- Kirkpatrick, James, undated (Box 94)
- Kirman, Albert P. Jr., undated (Box 94)
- Kirman, Albert D. Jr., undated (Box 94)
- Kirshenblatt, Gimblett Barbara, undated (Box 94)
- Kirschner, Harold, undated (Box 94)
- Kirtzman, Andrew, undated (Box 94)
- Kirzner, Israel M., undated (Box 94)
- Kitroeff, Alexander, undated (Box 94)
- Kittay, Jeffrey, undated (Box 94)
- Klaman, Saul B., undated (Box 94)
- Klapper, Hope, undated (Box 94)
- Klarman, Herbert, undated (Box 94)
- Klebenoff, Milton, undated (Box 94)
- Kleegman, Sophia J., undated (Box 94)
- Kleiman, Harlan, undated (Box 94)
- Klein, Bertrand, undated (Box 94)
- Klein, Frannie J., undated (Box 94)
- Klein, George S., undated (Box 94)
- Klein, George, undated (Box 95)
- Klein, Ira Edward, undated (Box 95)
- Klein, Dennis B., undated (Box 95)
- Klein, Harriet, undated (Box 95)
- Klein, Harold A., undated (Box 95)
- Klein, Jerome E., undated (Box 95)
- Klein, Jerome R., undated (Box 95)
- Klein, Phyllis, undated (Box 95)
- Klein, Robert L., undated (Box 95)
- Klein, Woody, undated (Box 95)
- Kleinfeld, Vincent A., undated (Box 95)
- Kleinman, Water J. Jr., undated (Box 95)
- Kleinman, Loui, undated (Box 95)
- Kleinschrod, Walter, undated (Box 95)
- Kleman, Susan, undated (Box 95)
- Klepp, Amela L., undated (Box 95)
- Klemin, Alexander, undated (Box 95)
- Klepper, Michael, undated (Box 95)
- Kleppner, Oto, undated (Box 95)
- Klibbe, Lawrence, undated (Box 95)
- Kline, Ira, undated (Box 95)
- Kline, Professor Morris, undated (Box 95)
- Kline, Morris, undated (Box 95)
- Klinenberg, Eric, undated (Box 95)
- Klosterman, J.A., undated (Box 95)
- Klotzburger, Katherine, undated (Box 95)
- Knauth, E. Frederic, undated (Box 95)
- Knedler, Dean John W. Jr., undated (Box 96)
- Knee, Bernard, undated (Box 96)
- Knighton, W.S., undated (Box 96)
- Knipe, Isobel M., undated (Box 96)
- Knitzer, Jane, undated (Box 96)
- Knopf, S. Adolphus, undated (Box 96)
- Knopping, Justin, undated (Box 96)
- Knowlton, Daniel C., undated (Box 96)
- Knox, Israel Dr., undated (Box 96)
- Knudsen, John, undated (Box 96)
- Kob, Walter, undated (Box 96)
- Kobak, Edgar, undated (Box 96)
- Koch, Adrienne, undated (Box 96)
- Koch, Robert, undated (Box 96)
- Koch, Edward I., undated (Box 96)
- Koch, Vivienne, undated (Box 96)
- Koch, Sigmund K., undated (Box 96)
- Kochevar, John (Journalism), undated (Box 96)
- Kodjak, Andrej (Slavic Language and Literature), undated (Box 96)
- Koehler, David, undated (Box 96)
- Koenig, Louis W., undated (Box 96)
- Koenigsknecht, Michael S. '76L, undated (Box 96)
- Kogan, Ellen (Dance, SEHNAP), undated (Box 96)
- Kohler, Robert H., undated (Box 96)
- Koeppen, Arthur Robert, undated (Box 96)
- Kogen, Arnold, undated (Box 96)
- Kohlerman, James H., undated (Box 96)
- Kohn, Alan M., undated (Box 96)
- Kohn, Hans, undated (Box 96)
- Kohn, Robert (Courant), undated (Box 96)
- Kohon, Harold, undated (Box 96)
- Kolff, Butch Van Breda, undated (Box 96)
- Koke, Richard J., undated (Box 96)
- Komarek, Kurt L., undated (Box 96)
- Komanoff, Hannah, undated (Box 96)
- Konvitz, Milton, undated (Box 96)
- Koo, Jeffrey, undated (Box 96)
- Kopac, Dr. Milan, undated (Box 96)
- Kopcke, Guenter, undated (Box 96)
- Kopelov, Connie, undated (Box 96)
- Kopp, Wendy, undated (Box 96)
- Kopta, William A., undated (Box 96)
- Koppenaal, Richard, undated (Box 96)
- Korff, Serge, undated (Box 97)
- Korff, Serge A., undated (Box 97)
- Korff, Dr. Serge A., undated (Box 97)
- Korin, Samuel B., undated (Box 97)
- Korkes, Solomon, undated (Box 97)
- Korman, Abraham K., undated (Box 97)
- Korman, Eleanore Z., undated (Box 97)
- Korn, Edward, undated (Box 97)
- Kornblum, Allen, undated (Box 97)
- Korner, Anthony, undated (Box 97)
- Kornhauser, Lewis, undated (Box 97)
- Kortepeter, C. Max, undated (Box 97)
- Kosak, Alvin I., undated (Box 97)
- Kosakoff, Gabiel, undated (Box 97)
- Kossman, Dr. Charles E., undated (Box 97)
- Kosterlitz, Hans, undated (Box 97)
- Kosterlanetz, Boris, undated (Box 98)
- Koten, Bernard, undated (Box 98)
- Kouri, Natasha, undated (Box 98)
- Kouri, Pentti J.K., undated (Box 98)
- Kove, Myron '56A, '67L, undated (Box 98)
- Kovner, Anthony R. (GPA), undated (Box 98)
- Kozin, Eugene M., undated (Box 98)
- Kraemer, Casper, undated (Box 98)
- Kraetzer, Warren, undated (Box 98)
- Kraft, Randy, undated (Box 98)
- Krag, Edith, undated (Box 98)
- Krakauer, Dr. Jay F., undated (Box 98)
- Kramer, Edith, undated (Box 98)